Guide to the Medical Society of the County of Monroe records, [1828-1961?].
Medical Society of the County of Monroe records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Medical Society of the County of Monroe records, [1828-1961?].
3083
Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc.
22 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Research Materials, Scrapbooks
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files of committees, minutes of meetings, reports, records of death associated with pregnancy and childbirth, constitution and bylaws as amended June 1876, financial records, pamphlets, and scrapbooks of the Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Medical Society of the County of Monroe was formed in 1821.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files of committees, minutes of meetings, reports, records of death associated with pregnancy and childbirth, constitution and bylaws as amended June 1876, financial records, pamphlets, and scrapbooks of the Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc.
Subjects:
Medicine--Societies, etc.
Places:
Monroe County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Minutes (administrative records); Constitutions.; Bylaws (administrative records); Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Records open only to qualified researchers approved by the President of the Board of Directors or the Executive Director of the Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc.
Dates in the guide below may be circa and not absolute in reference to the subject files.
CONTAINER LIST
- Subject files (committees), 1941-1953 (Box 1)
- Subject files (committees), 1937-1953 (Box 2)
- Subject files (committees - primarily public relations), 1949-1952 (Box 3)
- Subject files (sub-committees - primarily public relations), 1947-1955 (Box 4)
- Subject files, 1947-1957 (Box 5)
- Subject files, 1948-1957 (Box 6)
- Subject files, 1943-1960 (Box 7)
- Subject files (meetings and reports), 1948-1956 (Box 8)
- Subject files (primarily public relations), 1948-1957 (Box 9)
- Subject files, 1946-1958 (Box 10)
- Subject files (committee reports), 1953-1958 (Box 11)
- Subject files (primarily committee reports), 1953-1958 (Box 12)
- Subject files, 1954-1959 (Box 13)
- Subject files (primarily committee reports), 1957-1959 (Box 14)
- Subject files (primarily committee reports), 1958-1959 (Box 15)
- Subject files (records of deaths associated with pregnancy and childbirth), 1933-1947 (Box 16)
- Subject files, 1950-1960 (Box 17)
- Subject files (primarily grievance committee), 1950-1959 (Box 18)
- Subject files (primarily grievance committee) (Box 19)
- Constitution and by-laws as amended June 1876, 1876 (Box 19)
- Account book, 1828-1875 (Box 19)
- Board of Censors, minutes, 1906- (Box 19)
- Comitia Minora, 1906-1938 (Box 19)
- Minutes, June 9, 1875 - March 26, 1903 (Box 19)
- Minutes, May 1903 - March 1933 (Box 19)
- Pamphlets (socialized medicine) (Box 20)
- Scrapbook, 1949 (Box 20)
- Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 20)
- Scrapbook, 1950-1951 (Box 20)
- Scrapbook, 1955 (Box 20)
- Scrapbook, 1956 (Box 20)
- Financial record, 1955-1956 (Box 21)
- Scrapbooks, 1943-1948, 1951-1954 (Box 21)
- A. D. Kaiser Memorial Fund record book, 1954-1955 (Box 21)
- Financial record books, 1875-1934 (Box 22)